doriddles.com 2016-05-18

# Privacy & Security Policy of Do Quizzes

## Introduction

We're committed to protecting the privacy of your information. **We will never sell, misuse or exploit any information provided to us.** We collect information for the purpose of improving riddles and tracking our website via google analytics. Our privacy policy explains how we collect and treat this information. By using our services you acknowledge that you have reviewed and accepted the terms of our privacy policy. 

This privacy policy does not apply to separate entities which may utilize our riddles test as part of there services. 

## Copyright

We allow users to submit riddles both anonymously and via an account. If you believe on of our riddles infringes upon copyright please contact us with details of the riddle and originating source of the riddle. 

## Information Collection

The following describes the types of information collect during various interactions with our services.

### Account Information

During either Facebook or form account registration with Do Riddles Tested we may collect personally identifying information such as IP address, First, Last name and more. 

### Advertisements

Sometimes our riddles contain ads served via the Google Adsense network. 

## Security

### Information Storage

We store collected information in a secure SQL database and make every effort to ensure security against vulnerabilities. As with any web based platforms there are risks involved in transmitting information and while we undertake considerable effort to ensure security we cannot provide absolute assurance and so we encourage all users to exercise discretion when providing personal information. 

## Further Information

Should you require further clarification or have a suggestion in regards to our privacy policy please do not hesitate to get in contact with us
